SABLINA ANGULO LI



Barcelona, Spain. +34 616596861

e-mail: sablinahare@gmail.com

SUMMARY

23-year experienced English teacher with excellent communication skills. Able to work on own initiative and as part of a team. Proven leadership skills involving academic managing, mentoring, teacher recruitment and prospective teachers preparation. Uses effective and efficient methods of teaching whilst focusing on students' needs and interests. Believes Education is vital to improve and develop a person's life as well as our society.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Lesson planning.

- Classroom management.

- Teaching skills.

- Grammar instructions.

- Promoting inclusion.

- Subject knowledge.

- Mentoring teachers.

- Academic coordination.

- Meaningful lessons.

- Student assessment.

EXPERIENCE

2010 - to current.

Freelance English teacher. Barcelona.

- Gives private English lessons to all-level students with different needs and interests

such as passing English International Exams, English in the PAU Exam and

English exams at school; as well as helping students to improve their speaking skills.

2015 to May 2022.

iFP Grupo Planeta. Barcelona.

English teacher.

- Gave group English lessons to students of

different profession courses.

2015 to November 2022.

IEI Sant Andreu – Escuela Numor.Barcelona.

English teacher.

- Gave group and private English lessons to teens and adults, all levels, including PET,

FCE, CAE and CPE preparation.

2010 to 2015

Master Spain School. Barcelona.

English and Spanish teacher. Teachers'

mentor. Academic Coordinator.

-Taught Spanish to groups from France and Germany in 3-hour sessions focusing on language awareness and topic discussions.

- Taught English to all-level groups and one-to-one classes based on differentiated learning needs and goals.
- Prepared students for English International Exams (PET, FCE, CAE) and the English Test in the PAU Exam.
- Coordinated and planned each academic year, assigned classes to teachers and arranged schedules.
- Elaborated the school evaluation system and prepared exams.
- Tutored and helped teachers develop their teaching skills, deal with class management problems and students' assessment.
- Evaluated and selected new teachers and gave them induction sessions.
- Classified new students according to their English level.

2000 - 2008

El Cultural Binational Center of Trujillo. Peru.

English teacher, Teachers' Mentor, Academic Coordinator.

- Taught English to 25-student groups of all levels.
- Used communicative and TBL activities to maximize meaningful learning and students' participation.
- Tutored teachers and helped them with lesson planning, communicative activities and teaching skills.
- Coordinated the Satursunday programme, evaluated prospective teachers and conducted the Induction programme for new teachers.
- Gave workshops on Motivation.
- Classified new students according to their English level.
- Hosted non-academic events at the center such as Christmas shows.

2001 – 2002 Universidad Privada Antenor Orrego.

Trujillo, Peru. English teacher.

- Taught English to university students and professors of all levels at the Language

Center of the university.

1995 - 2000 Several radio stations in Trujillo. Peru.

- Co-directed, co-produced and

co-presented the radio program "La Tierra y

la Vida" to develop environmental

awareness.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

B.A. in Education 1995 – 1999 Universidad Nacional de Trujillo. Peru.

OTHERS

- Native Spanish speaker.
- ECCE and ECPE (Competence and Proficiency Michigan Certificates).
- Basic level of Catalan Certificate.
- Basic French.
- Driving License B.

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Assertive. - Excellent communicator.

- Well-organized.- Proactive.- Problem solving.- Committed.

- Hardworking. - Eager to learn and improve.

REFERENCES

- Available on request.